I think it's about time we've had an
honest conversation about, I guess the
elephant in the room, if you will.
Whereas there's a lot of you that are
struggling financially when it comes to
credit, when it comes to paying off
bills, when it comes to being in deeper
debt than maybe you've ever experienced
in your life.
And then not making enough cash flow,
not making enough money. And so over the
years, over the last 20 something years
since I've been training people, and
over the last 30 plus years that I've
been an entrepreneur, I've noticed one
common thread with most people that just
never find the success that they're
looking for in their life.
And that is this.
The common thread is that they kind of
want to do the money making stuff first.
They want to implement the plan first.
Now, by the way, there's nothing wrong
with trying to implement a money making
plan. However, if your mindset's not
there yet, no matter what you do, no
matter what you try, no matter what you
try to push forth into trying to make
successful, just never turns out to be a
successful.
And I was there once. I was there once a
long, long time ago, when I myself was
trying to find ways of building wealth
for myself.
You know, I I I was trying to do the
wealth stuff first. Trying to buy the
business plans first. Trying to buy
every single type of, you know, money
making thing on every infomercial you
can think of. This was back in the day.
I don't even know, do they still have
infomercials nowadays? But, you know, I
used to buy all that stuff. $39.95 for
this, and the Don Lapre program, and the
Carlton Sheets program, and all these
different programs to find the ultimate
road map to wealth, and then nothing
ever worked out. Now, mind you, a lot of
those things are just shim-shams anyway,
just to be able to take money from you.
But, some wealth plans are pretty solid.
It's just that the problem is if your
mindset is all wrong, and you have a
broke mindset, then you're never going
to be successful no no matter what you
do.
So, how do you get past the broke
mindset? The mindset that puts you in
the financial despair in the first place
that maybe you're experiencing right
now.
And the answer is a very simple book,
believe it or not, and a book that I
want to give you 100% for free. I want
to give you the download version of this
book. It's called Deliberate
Manifestation. It's a book that I I
wrote years ago. In fact, if you want a
free copy of this, you can get the PDF
download 100% free at my school
community, which is
school.com/monicamayne,
all lowercase. And once you're admitted
into the group, which typically takes
about 24 hours, go on up to the
classroom tab at the top of the page,
look for Deliberate Manifestation.
Now, there's one particular area that I
love in this book. In fact, you can see
my little makeshift bookmark. It's a
million-dollar bill, which isn't real,
but
I like to have that kind of stuff around
to be able to, I guess,
you know, not motivate me necessarily,
but remind me that abundance is
literally everywhere. And it is
literally everywhere, you guys. If you
are in the United States of America or
any English-speaking first-world
country, and you're not able to make it
big on a financial level, there's
something wrong with you, because the
opportunity is literally everywhere. So,
the only thing that's wrong with you,
really, is what's going on between those
two ears of yours, and that is you
aren't thinking the right way. So, one
of the things I want to address, and
this is on page 92 of the book, so when
you get the book for free at
school.com/monicamayne,
all lowercase,
you will be able to download this, and
you'll be able to see this particular
part of the book and many other parts of
this book where I talk about exactly
how to do manifestation. Now, if you
think that manifestation is some woo-woo
thing, think again. Some of the top
multi-millionaires, billionaires, and
now our first trillionaire, Elon Musk,
they all do this kind of stuff,
inadvertently or
directly, where they'll sit down. I
mean, Steve Jobs was a huge believer in
Yogananda, and he used to read his book
endlessly, and talked about meditation,
and talked about focus in, you know,
doing the law of attraction stuff. So,
if you think it's some woo-woo thing
that nobody does at that level, think
again. They're all doing it at that
level. They're just not sharing it with
you because if they did share it with
you, well, then everybody would be doing
it.
They would lose out on all their worker
bees and they would have nobody to
basically run and manage their their
wealth-building dream of theirs. So,
that's why a lot of these big-time, you
know, multi-billionaires don't talk
about this kind of thing because they
really don't want you to know about
this. In fact, this goes back to the
days of like Henry Ford, for example.
Even going back further to Rockefeller,
>> [snorts]
>> who actually created the school board in
1903 1902, rather,
to
basically create worker bees. He didn't
want anybody to know how to build
wealth. He wanted people to be on a
brainwashed schedule of getting
somewhere on a certain day of the week,
Monday through Friday, of course, at a
certain time. You have lunch at a
certain time, have breaks at a certain
time, leave at a certain time, and
starting the process of brainwashing
you. So, then that way when you go into
the workforce after you graduate high
school or college,
guess what? You're already brainwashed
into the system.
He did that on purpose. So, the
billionaires, they don't they don't want
you to know how to control your destiny,
but I do. And I kind of cracked the code
here with this book. So, let me go back
to page 92 here.
In fact, [snorts] you can't even get the
physical copy. This is the last known
physical copy on Earth that is
available, and I have it, and nobody can
have it. Maybe if you offer me $10,000,
I would give it to you, but other than
that, you can't have this book. So, page
talks exactly about the steps on
manifestation and exactly what to do
when it comes specifically to
manifesting manifesting
from a business perspective because you
do have to have some kind of
wealth-building plan. So, I talk about
it right here about writing not only
just writing specific goals down
So, I use an example of like say $10,000
a month, maybe that you want to make in
profits or in the very beginning
probably as gross revenues.
And then what you want to do is this is
beyond I guess just visualization, this
particular strategy that I talk about in
this book. By the way, this book is
probably my most successful book when it
comes to manifestation. I do have
another book here. Where is it? Oh, it's
over here.
It's on the other side. I don't have a
lot of these left either. You could also
get this for free at
school.com/monicamein.
This was my later book that I did years
later after deliberate manifestation.
However, the publisher of this book,
Waterside, who published this book for
me, they're in Carlsbad, Califor- I
think Carlsbad, somewhere in Southern
California.
And they didn't let me put some of the
things that I put into this book, which
is a self-published book.
So, even though this is a really good
book, which you can again also get for
free in the classroom tab at
school.com/monicamein,
this one doesn't include some of the
things that I was able to include here
because I was uncensored, okay? It's
amazing what happens when you're
censored. So, you don't tell people
things. So,
I talk about that in 92. But most
importantly, most importantly, I So, let
me tell you a little bit about myself
just really quick. I am a self-help
junkie. I have been since the beginning
of time. I've read all the law of
attraction, manifestation, self-helpy
types of books out there
over the years, over the decades. And
what I talk about on page 104 in
particular
is incredible because this particular
technique combined with the
visualization that I talk about in the
book,
there's a specific technique you can use
to kind of accelerate manifestation in
your life in a way that it's almost
magical in quality. And you wouldn't
really understand exactly what I'm
talking about until you actually go to
page 104 in this book.
And so I don't want to go into the
details exactly about how to do it, but
in order for you to manifest what you
want, you're going to have to obviously
have a goal. So, I gave you an idea,
$10,000 a month, maybe with your own
online internet-based business or
something to that effect. And then what
you can do is start the process of doing
the techniques and strategies I talk
about on page 104, which is really
magical in quality and allows you to
accelerate on such a quick level the
things that you really truly want in
your life, okay? And again, this is the
uncensored version of The Lost Secret,
which I wrote many, many years later,
okay?
So, if you want this uncensored version,
the version where my publisher didn't
allow me to have some of the things that
I really wanted to add into The Lost
Secret that are all here, then again, go
to school.com/monicamein.
Look for it under the classroom tab. I'm
not going to keep it up there for
forever. So, hopefully you get it before
I take it down because once it comes
down, that's it. I'm not going to be
offering it anymore. It's just not going
to be there anymore. And I guess it'll
be a secret that I take to my grave as
well as the thousands of other people
that were able to actually get this book
before I took it down forever, okay?
Some lucky people actually have the
physical version of this. You know, we
we had several thousand of these over
the years that went out with different
covers on it, but it's just
everybody always asks like what is your
biggest success secret? And I would like
to tell you that it has something to do
with business, but really it doesn't.
The biggest success secret is here in
deliberate manifestation, which again,
you can get for free.
So, I would start here. It's not with
the business plan, you guys. It's not
with the wealth road map. It's not with
the blueprint, the secret guru strategy.
It's not doesn't start there.
It starts with
beyond mindset. It's almost like
you're kind of tapping into the pulse of
I guess the universe if that makes sense
and understanding exactly how to do that
through meditation, through deep
breathing, and through most importantly
visualization. And once you master that
then literally anything and everything
that you want kind of comes to you
automatically by default as easily as if
you're falling off a log. That's how
quick and fast and easy it happens. And
that's the way it should be.
Lis- Listen, life should not be a
struggle. It should not be feeling like
swimming upstream at all times. And if
you're feeling like that
you're feeling anxiety-ridden, stressed
out, you know, in debt, don't know
what's going to happen next.
Some of you might not want to live
another day, which please don't don't do
that. I mean, don't.
You have everything to live for. You
have every opportunity. You just need to
open your eyes and and know what to look
for when it comes to opportunity because
opportunity is everywhere. If you're
listening to my voice, you can
understand what I'm saying
then opportunity is abundant and
everywhere for you. You just have to
know it and believe it and then
implement the steps that I talk about in
this book. Listen, this is the book.
This is the book. If you want to change
everything virtually overnight, then you
need to read this. So, get it now while
you still can, while it's still
available. school.com/monicamein
All [snorts] lowercase. You will find it
in the classroom tab.
And hopefully you get it in time because
I will be taking it down soon. So,
hopefully you found that this content
was useful. If so, give me a nice thumbs
up, subscribe to my channel, drop some
comments down below. This is Monica Mein
signing off and I will see you in the
next video.